<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>The Swashbuckle Blog</title>
    <description>The Lendablog</description>
    <link>http://yourdomain.com/blog/</link>
    <atom:link href="http://yourdomain.com/blog/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <pubDate>Tue, 17 Nov 2015 00:50:17 -0500</pubDate>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 17 Nov 2015 00:50:17 -0500</lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Jekyll v2.5.3</generator>
    
      <item>
        <title>Accurate, but irrelevant</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;I love economics so much.  I mean really, is there any other &quot;academic discipline&quot; that combines astrology, heresay, hunches and witchraft, and yet still gets a Nobel every year?  Economics is the farking beez-kneez, bitch.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Which brings me to my next point: currency.  &quot;Currency&quot; from the latin &quot;current&quot; meaning that moment in the conversation when everyone realizes someone farted, but nobody wants to talk bout it. Not really going anywhere with that.  I just find that starting all discussions of any topic with a quick &quot;from the latin...&quot; makes me look smart.  And chicks dig it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So, what's so significant about currency?  Or better, what's so current about significancy?!?!  Aha - you didn't see that coming, did you?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;An old wise man once told a shopkeeper, &quot;if you keep your savings in gold, then the government will tax you; if you keep your savings in rice, then you will be tempted to eat it. But, if you keep your savings in this &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.tierrayucatan.com/listings/en/4&quot;&gt;once-in-a-lifetime real estate investment opportunity&lt;/a&gt;, then you will be rich and all the girls will love you.  &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I'm &quot;legally obligated&quot; to tell you that Swashbuckle has a professional agreement with the above real estate agency.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 class=&quot;section-heading&quot;&gt;Currency is the only thing that matters&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Really, it is.  Screw Christmas, forget your marital vows, and park in the handicapped spot, cause if it ain't currency, I ain't listening!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For real!  If you don't believe me, look at the below chart.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;#&quot;&gt;
    &lt;img src=&quot;/blog/img/currency/currency3.JPG&quot; alt=&quot;This chart took me literally 9 hours to create.&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;span class=&quot;caption text-muted&quot;&gt;The line is going up.  Or down.  It depends which side you start on.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;See how the line is trending towards the axis at which the radial galapogos goose goes going?  What I mean to say is that the Ugandan, er, money is being increasingly increased while the American, uh, deflation!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Which brings me to my next point.  Human travel to Mars is not as inevitable as some would make you think.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 class=&quot;section-heading&quot;&gt;Mars?  Forget about it!&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;#&quot;&gt;
    &lt;img src=&quot;/blog/img/currency/currency2.JPG&quot; alt=&quot;Emi Savaggio is so smart&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;span class=&quot;caption text-muted&quot;&gt;Coffee is the motor that keeps the economy running.  All swashbucklers know that.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;All this talk about Mars.  Mars this, mars that.  Why the obsession with this inhospitable wasteland.  Proximity?  If we wanted close, we'd move to New Jersey, not Mars!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Plus, Jupiter isn't really that far away.  See?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;#&quot;&gt;
    &lt;img src=&quot;/blog/img/currency/currency4.JPG&quot; alt=&quot;Planets!  &quot; /&gt;
&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;span class=&quot;caption text-muted&quot;&gt;Earth and Jupiter.  Not to scale..&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I say we go to Jupiter, first.  Jupiter has many advantageous advantages.  It has three nice-sounding syllables, beautiful rings, and it is the only planet after which NONE of the seven dwarves are named! &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Gotta go! &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Photographs by &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.theguardian.com/environment/2008/jun/07/bottlenose.dolphin&quot;&gt;Joe Brew&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

</description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 16 Nov 2015 07:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>http://yourdomain.com/blog/2015/11/16/currency/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://yourdomain.com/blog/2015/11/16/currency/</guid>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Please give me your data</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Hi again!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It's me, Joe, from Swashbuckle.  We exchanged a few emails a couple months ago.  And then I exchanged some, by myself.  Well, I sent them to you, but you never wrote back.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Weeks passed, then the weeks became fortnights (I just learned that word, isn't it cool, it makes me sound British, doesn't it!?), then the fortnights (awesome word!) became months. No reply.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I occasionally would open some of the emails I had sent you, to see if perhaps I had said something offensive, but nope, they were pretty vanilla.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 class=&quot;section-heading&quot;&gt;Why won't you just give me your data?&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You sounded so excited on the phone. You were like &quot;yeah, let's do this, cool!&quot; and I was like &quot;alright, yeah, great!&quot;  Such positive energy, man!  I was so pumped after our call that I kicked a baby!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;(Don't worry, it wasn't some stranger's baby.  This was a baby that's been hanging around my house for a while, acting weird and stuff.)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;#&quot;&gt;
    &lt;img src=&quot;/blog/img/data_please/data_please_2.JPG&quot; alt=&quot;I can't really think of any way in which this photo is relevant&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;span class=&quot;caption text-muted&quot;&gt;Imagine, you and me, playing the data-for-in-kind-analysis marimba together, forever.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Anyway, so, what happened?  I mean, did you meet someone else to whom you're gonna give your data?  Am I being overbearing?  Underbearing?  Do you want me to better balance my bearing?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 class=&quot;section-heading&quot;&gt;Do you want to talk about it?&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Listen, I get it.  These things happen.  Sometimes people offer data, and then they act like big old jerks.  C'est la vie, right?  No big deal.  &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;#&quot;&gt;
    &lt;img src=&quot;/blog/img/data_please/data_please_3.JPG&quot; alt=&quot;So many photos in this post&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;span class=&quot;caption text-muted&quot;&gt;Don’t worry, I’ll never hang you out to dry.  (Get it?  Cause the photo…)&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;But, do you think we could, you know, just have a cup of coffee together and talk about it?  I know you're really busy and stuff, but I just want some closure, you know?  I mean if you're really busy, it's okay, that's fine, no worries.  Yeah, I'm pretty busy too.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I miss you.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Tue, 10 Nov 2015 07:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>http://yourdomain.com/blog/2015/11/10/data_please/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://yourdomain.com/blog/2015/11/10/data_please/</guid>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>I believe that everyone should be able to dunk</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Every human being on earth, from the smallest newborn to Hulk Hogan, should be able to dunk a basketball.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Why do I believe this?  Great question!  First, it's because I can dunk a basketball.  If I can dunk, so can you!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Second, it's because I firmly belive in equal opportunity.  Which is why everyone should have the opportunity to dunk. And if they're not as tall as me, they should have the opportunity to grow.  And then dunk!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Did I mention that I can dunk a basketball?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Third, and perhaps most importantly, dunking brings us closer to the sky, literally, which is where Santa Claus and Michael Jackson are.  Plus, I once read that if we all dunk at the same time, there will be a massive earthquake.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;(But none of us will feel it, because we'll be in the air DUNKING)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Aren't Jun out!&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Sat, 07 Nov 2015 07:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>http://yourdomain.com/blog/2015/11/07/i-believe/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://yourdomain.com/blog/2015/11/07/i-believe/</guid>
        
        
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
